http://www.primalmuscle.com/terms_privacy.asp

Introduction
Welcome to www.primalmuscle.com. This website is owned and operated by Ultimate Fitness Nutrition, Inc. By visiting our website and accessing the information, resources, services, products, and tools we provide, you understand and agree to accept and adhere to the following terms and conditions as stated in this policy (hereafter referred to as 'User Agreement'), along with the terms and conditions as stated in our Privacy Policy (please refer to the Privacy Policy section below for more information).
This agreement is in effect as of Aug 30, 2012.
We reserve the right to change this User Agreement from time to time without notice. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this User Agreement periodically to familiarize yourself with any modifications. Your continued use of this site after such modifications will constitute acknowledgment and agreement of the modified terms and conditions.
Responsible Use and Conduct
By visiting our website and accessing the information, resources, services, products, and tools we provide for you, either directly or indirectly (hereafter referred to as 'Resources'), you agree to use these Resources only for the purposes intended as permitted by (a) the terms of this User Agreement, and (b) applicable laws, regulations and generally accepted online practices or guidelines.
Wherein, you understand that:
a. In order to access our Resources, you may be required to provide certain information about yourself (such as identification, contact details, etc.) as part of the registration process, or as part of your ability to use the Resources. You agree that any information you provide will always be accurate, correct, and up to date.
b. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any login information associated with any account you use to access our Resources. Accordingly, you are responsible for all activities that occur under your account/s.
c. Accessing (or attempting to access) any of our Resources by any means other than through the means we provide, is strictly prohibited. You specifically agree not to access (or attempt to access) any of our Resources through any automated, unethical or unconventional means.
d. Engaging in any activity that disrupts or interferes with our Resources, including the servers and/or networks to which our Resources are located or connected, is strictly prohibited.
e. Attempting to copy, duplicate, reproduce, sell, trade, or resell our Resources is strictly prohibited.
f. You are solely responsible any consequences, losses, or damages that we may directly or indirectly incur or suffer due to any unauthorized activities conducted by you, as explained above, and may incur criminal or civil liability.
g. We may provide various open communication tools on our website, such as blog comments, blog posts, public chat, forums, message boards, newsgroups, product ratings and reviews, various social media services, etc. You understand that generally we do not pre-screen or monitor the content posted by users of these various communication tools, which means that if you choose to use these tools to submit any type of content to our website, then it is your personal responsibility to use these tools in a responsible and ethical manner. By posting information or otherwise using any open communication tools as mentioned, you agree that you will not upload, post, share, or otherwise distribute any content that:
i. Is illegal, threatening, defamatory, abusive, harassing, degrading, intimidating, fraudulent, deceptive, invasive, racist, or contains any type of suggestive, inappropriate, or explicit language; ii. Infringes on any trademark, patent, trade secret, copyright, or other proprietary right of any party; Iii. Contains any type of unauthorized or unsolicited advertising; Iiii. Impersonates any person or entity, including any www.primalmuscle.com employees or representatives.
We have the right at our sole discretion to remove any content that, we feel in our judgment does not comply with this User Agreement, along with any content that we feel is otherwise offensive, harmful, objectionable, inaccurate, or violates any 3rd party copyrights or trademarks. We are not responsible for any delay or failure in removing such content. If you post content that we choose to remove, you hereby consent to such removal, and consent to waive any claim against us.
h. We do not assume any liability for any content posted by you or any other 3rd party users of our website. However, any content posted by you using any open communication tools on our website, provided that it doesn't violate or infringe on any 3rd party copyrights or trademarks, becomes the property of www.primalmuscle.com, and as such, gives us a perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, royalty-free, exclusive license to reproduce, modify, adapt, translate, publish, publicly display and/or distribute as we see fit. This only refers and applies to content posted via open communication tools as described, and does not refer to information that is provided as part of the registration process, necessary in order to use our Resources. All information provided as part of our registration process is covered by our privacy policy.
i. You agree to indemnify and hold harmless www.primalmuscle.com and its parent company and affiliates, and their directors, officers, managers, employees, donors, agents, and licensors, from and against all losses, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys' fees, resulting from any violation of this User Agreement or the failure to fulfill any obligations relating to your account incurred by you or any other person using your account. We reserve the right to take over the exclusive defense of any claim for which we are entitled to indemnification under this User Agreement. In such event, you shall provide us with such cooperation as is reasonably requested by us.
Privacy
Your privacy is very important to us, which is why we've created a separate Privacy Policy in order to explain in detail how we collect, manage, process, secure, and store your private information. Our privacy policy is included under the scope of this User Agreement. To read our privacy policy in its entirety, click here.
Limitation of Warranties
By using our website, you understand and agree that all Resources we provide are "as is" and "as available". This means that we do not represent or warrant to you that: i) the use of our Resources will meet your needs or requirements. ii) the use of our Resources will be uninterrupted, timely, secure or free from errors. iii) the information obtained by using our Resources will be accurate or reliable, and iv) any defects in the operation or functionality of any Resources we provide will be repaired or corrected.
Furthermore, you understand and agree that:
v) any content downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of our Resources is done at your own discretion and risk, and that you are solely responsible for any damage to your computer or other devices for any loss of data that may result from the download of such content. vi) no information or advice, whether expressed, implied, oral or written, obtained by you from www.primalmuscle.com or through any Resources we provide shall create any warranty, guarantee, or conditions of any kind, except for those expressly outlined in this User Agreement.
Limitation of Liability
In conjunction with the Limitation of Warranties as explained above, you expressly understand and agree that any claim against us shall be limited to the amount you paid, if any, for use of products and/or services. www.primalmuscle.com will not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or exemplary loss or damages which may be incurred by you as a result of using our Resources, or as a result of any changes, data loss or corruption, cancellation, loss of access, or downtime to the full extent that applicable limitation of liability laws apply.
Copyrights/Trademarks
All content and materials available on www.primalmuscle.com, including but not limited to text, graphics, website name, code, images and logos are the intellectual property of www.primalmuscle.com, and are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law. Any inappropriate use, including but not limited to the reproduction, distribution, display or transmission of any content on this site is strictly prohibited, unless specifically authorized by www.primalmuscle.com.
Termination of Use
You agree that we may, at our sole discretion, suspend or terminate your access to all or part of our website and Resources with or without notice and for any reason, including, without limitation, breach of this User Agreement. Any suspected illegal, fraudulent or abusive activity may be grounds for terminating your relationship and may be referred to appropriate law enforcement authorities. Upon suspension or termination, your right to use the Resources we provide will immediately cease, and we reserve the right to remove or delete any information that you may have on file with us, including any account or login information.
Governing Law
This website is controlled by www.primalmuscle.com from our offices located in the state of FL, USA. It can be accessed by most countries around the world. As each country has laws that may differ from those of FL, by accessing our website, you agree that the statutes and laws of FL, without regard to the conflict of laws and the United Nations Convention on the International Sales of Goods, will apply to all matters relating to the use of this website and the purchase of any products or services through this site.
Furthermore, any action to enforce this User Agreement shall be brought in the federal or state courts located in USA, FL You hereby agree to personal jurisdiction by such courts, and waive any jurisdictional, venue, or inconvenient forum objections to such courts.
Guarantee
UNLESS OTHERWISE EXPRESSED, www.primalmuscle.com EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.
Marketing Communication:I expressly authorize Primal Muscle to call, fax, email, and/or text me with offers, advertisements and other solicitations (Promotions). I expressly understand and agree that these Promotions maybe delivered through use of automated technology, automatic telephone dialing system or an artificial or prerecorded voice. I expressly understand that I am not required to sign this agreement, and am not required to agree to the receipt of such calls, faxes and/or text messages, as a condition of purchasing any property, goods or services.
By signing up you agree to receive marketing calls, faxes, emails, and/or text messages, which may be sent through an automatic telephone dialing system, from Primal Muscle at the number provided. Consent is not required to purchase goods or services.
To opt of these messages - please contact our offices in writing.
Contact Information
http://www.primalmuscle.com1811 Englewood Rd. Ste 288Englewood FL 34223USA info@primalmuscle.com 1-800-535-9858
The Primal Advantage
Join the thousands of die-hard Primal Muscle clients who have discovered what full-service fitness consultation is all about.
Our Fitness Advisors can help you dial in your diet, training and supplements...
FREE of charge.
Give Us A Call, Or Drop Us A Line!
Company Information
About Us
Contact Us
Return/Refund Policy
Share Your Results!
Prop 65 Info
Prop 65
The Legal Stuff
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
© 2020 Primal Muscle.
Powered by Shopify
*Offers and discounts may be withdrawn at any time. User results may not be typical and may vary and the people featured have been remunerated. Use as directed along with a sensible nutrition and exercise program. Do not take more than the recommended dose on the label. As with prescription drugs there may be undesired side effects. Before using any dietary supplement contact your doctor, especially if you have any medical condition or are taking any medication. This information and these products have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration as they are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease. Active ingredients of these products may or may not have conclusive clinical medical studies from medical and/or regulatory authorities.
